export default [
    {
        question: 'Question 1',
        answer: 'Answer 1'
    },
    {
        question: 'Question 2',
        answer: 'Answer 2'
    },
    {
        question: 'Question 3',
        answer: 'Answer 3'
    },
    {
        question: 'Question 4',
        answer: 'Answer 4'
    },
    {
        question: 'Question 5',
        answer: 'Answer 5'
    },
    {
        question: 'Question 6',
        answer: 'Answer 6'
    },
    {
        question: 'Question 7',
        answer: 'Answer 7'
    },
    {
        question: 'Question 8',
        answer: 'Answer 8'
    },
    {
        question: 'Question 9',
        answer: 'Answer 9'
    },
    {
        question: 'Question 10',
        answer: 'Answer 10'
    }

];